<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="key_vibration">KEY_VIBRATION</string>
    <string name="key_suono_errore">KEY_SUONO_ERRORE</string>
    <string name="key_suono_corretto">KEY_SUONO_CORRETTO</string>
    <string name="key_pressure_preference">KEY_PRESSURE_PREFERENCE</string>
    <string name="key_info_pressure_preference">KEY_INFO_PRESSURE_PREFERENCE</string>
    <string name="key_pressure_checkbox">KEY_PRESSURE_CHECKPRESSURE</string>
    <string name="key_show_test_button">KEY_SHOW_TEST_BUTTON</string>
    <string name="key_csv_info">KEY_CSV_INFO</string>
    
    
	<string name="app_name">Iowa Gambling Task</string>
	<string name="choice">Choice:</string>
	<string name="net_gain">Net Gain:</string>
	<string name="penalty">Penalty:</string>
	<string name="titolo_gambling">Select deck by touching</string>
	<string name="finish">
	    Thank you for partecipating in the experiment. You may now leave. 
		Please alert the experimenter that you are done.
	</string>
	<string name="profilo_delle_carte_selezionate">Profile of selected cards</string>		
	<string name="reset">Reset</string>
	<string name="select_deck_by_touching">Select deck by touching</string>
	<string name="finish_titolo">Finish</string>
	<string name="total_number_of_cards">Total number of cards selected from each deck</string>
	<string name="minuti"> min</string>
	<string name="ore"> hours</string>
	<string name="tempo_impiegato">Time:</string>
	<string name="error_no_sd">No SD card\nImpossible save</string>
	<string name="api_level_nopdf">You can not save PDF\nPNG file will be saved
	</string>
	<string name="reward">Reward:</string>
	<string name="total">Total: $</string>
	<string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
	<string name="hai_guadagnato">You earned a total of:</string>
	<string name="enter_participant_identifier">Enter Participant Identifier</string>
	<string name="spiegazione1">
	    You are about to take part in an experiment on decision making.
	    You will start with a $2000 loan.
		On each trial, you will select a card from one of four decks.
		After you select each card,
		you will be given a reward and possibly be required to pay penalty.
		Your goal is to maximize the profit on your loan,
		and you may choose any deck at any time to do so.
		Touch to continue
	</string>
	<string name="spiegazione2">
		You are about to take part in an experiment on decision making.
		For each card you draws, you will get a reward.
		This reward depends on the deck you choose, and each deck has a fixed reward.
		You will also get a penalty, which will cost you money.
		Penalties are somewhat random;
		the penalty you will get is different for different cards in the deck.
		Sometimes the penalty will be zero,
		and sometimes it will be larger,
		at times even larger than the reward you get for choosing that deck.
		You will start with a $2000 loan and you should try to get as much money as
		possible by the end of the study.
		<!-- Touch to start -->
	</string>
	<string name="spiegazione3">
	    At the bottom of the screen, there is a graph which
		shows you your current earnings. 
		The more money you have, the larger the bar will be.
		\nNow, you will begin the test.\nDo you have any question?
		\nTouch to continue
	</string>
	<string name="start">Start </string>
	<string name="grafico">Charts</string>
	<string name="grafico1">Chart 1</string>
	<string name="grafico2">Chart 2</string>
	<string name="exit">Exit</string>
	<string name="salva">Save Pdf</string>
	<string name="salva_csv">Save Csv</string>
	<string name="salvato">Saved</string>
	<string name="info">Info</string>
	<string name="help">Help</string>
	<string name="about_message1">
	    This program reproduces the neuropsychological tests called \&quot;Iowa gambling task\&quot;,
		described for the first time in:
		\n BECHARA, A., DAMASIO, A.R., DAMASIO, H. e ANDERSON, S. (1994),
		Insensitivity to future consequences following damage to human prefrontal cortex.
		Cognition, n. 50, pp. 7-12.
		\n\nThis work is licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported.
		To view a copy of this license, 
		visit:\nhttp://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/3.0 or send a letter
		to Creative Commons, 171 Second Street, Suite 300, San Francisco,
		California, 94105, USA.
		\nThis program is distribuited \&quot;As Is\&quot; in the hope that it will be useful, 
		but WHITOUT ANY WARRANTY.
		\n\nThe libraries used for the chart are
		available:\nhttp://www.achartengine.org
		\n\nThe libraries
		used to save
		the pdf files are
		available:\nhttp://itextpdf.com/itext.php
		
		\n\nThanks to The working
		group for the chart icons in the
		menu:\nhttp://blog.twg.ca/2010/11/retina-display-icon-set
		
		\n\nThanks to Honza Dousek for the Save-Pdf and Save-Csv icons in the menu:
		\nhttps://www.iconfinder.com/Lexter
				
		\n\nThanks to David Bellot for the cards:
		\nhttp://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Card_back_01.svg
		
		\n\nThanks to <i><b>Rodrigo Hohl</b></i> for the Portuguese translation.
		
		\n\n\nExplanation of the required permissions:		
		\n1)Storage: the device can save a PDF file on the sd card.
		\n2)Hardware controls: the device can vibrate.
		
		\n\nIf you find bug, you want send same
		suggestions or request custom app,
		feel free to
		contact:\nzsimolabs@gmail.com
		\n
	</string>

	<string name="help_message1">
	    This app is designed to run the \&quot;Iowa Gambling
		task\&quot; on smartphone and tablet with Android.
		\nOn startup, after the screen to enter the name of the subject, you will
		see a brief explanation of the experiment.
		\nWe chose to not include in this app material about theoretical or technical
		details concerning this procedure in order to avoid the risk of
		influencing the experimental subjects.
		For information, please refer to the article which this application is based:
		\nBECHARA A., DAMASIO A.R., DAMASIO H. e ANDERSON S. (1994), Insensitivity to future
		consequences following damage to human prefrontal cortex. Cognition, n. 50, pp. 7-12.
		\n\nThe interface has been simplified by removing the task bar on the screens
		in which the subjects use the terminal, so that they are not distracted by the 
		contents of the terminal.
		At the end of the procedure, pressing the menu button, 
		the researcher can see 2 charts containing a summary of the results, save a PDF file and 
		a CSV file with all the raw data.
		The files will be saved to the sd card of the device in the folder named \&quot;iowa\&quot;;
		the name of the files will be: \&quot;iowa\&quot; + the first two letters of
		subject name + the date.
		Device with Android Eclair 2.1 (api level 7) or previous can save 2 PNG
		files with charts instead of the PDF file.
		
		\n\nIn the settings menu you can select the experimental options 
		(not present in the above-mentioned article) such as: associate a sound 
		or a short vibration (vibration is not avaible on Motorola Xoom) to winnings 
		and losses, show the progression of the selections.
		
		\n\nVersion 1.7 introduced the ability to export all the data recorded in a CSV file; 
		the data are:\n
		- participant\'s name\n
		- trial number\n
		- selected deck\n
		- reward\n
		- penalty\n
		- net gain\n
		- total earned\n
		- response time (the interval in milliseconds between trials)\n
		- pressure put on display (if enabled)\n
		- pressure style (if enabled)\n
		- touch speed (for how many milliseconds the finger is in contact with the display)\n
		- time\n
		- date\n
		
	</string>
	<string name="pi_di_un_giorno">more than a day</string>
	<string name="meno_di_un_minuto">less than a minute</string>
	<string name="introduzione">Introduction</string>
	<string name="settings">Settings</string>
	<string name="vibration">Vibration</string>
	<string name="vibrazione_subtitle">Short vibration if the penalty is larger than the reward</string>
	<string name="suono_errore">Penality sound</string>
	<string name="suono_corretto">Reward sound</string>
	<string name="suono_errore_summary">Play sound if the penalty is larger than the reward</string>
	<string name="suono_corretto_summary">
	    Play sound even if the reward is larger than the penalty
	</string>
	<string name="ver_number">1.7.2</string>
	<string name="nome">Name</string>
	<string name="tempo">Time</string>
	<string name="score">Score</string>
	<string name="about">About</string>
	<string name="key_preference_category_effetti">KEY_PREFERENCE_CATEGORY_EFFETTI</string>
	<string name="make_donation">Make a donation</string>
	<string name="key_donazione_preference">KEY_DONAZIONE_PREFERENCEa</string>
	<string name="donazione_summary">This application is free and without advertising.
	    If it is helpful and if you deem it appropriate, 
	    you can contribute to the work of the developer making a donation.
	</string>
	<string name="donazione">donation</string>
	<string name="paypal_input_error">ERROR\nNot a correct value</string>
	<string name="testo_donazione">Enter what you want to donate (in EURO) and click on the yellow button below</string>
	<string name="grazie_donazione">Thanks for donating!</string>
	<string name="donazione_operazione_annullata">Operation canceled</string>
	<string name="effect">Research Options</string>
	<string name="contribuisci">Contribute</string>
	<string name="changelog">ChangeLog</string>
	<string name="key_about_preference">KEY_ABOUT_PREFERENCE</string>
	<string name="changelog_testo">
	    	1.7.2:
	    	\nFixed bug in the order of the labels in the first chart.
	    	\nFixed month number in the name of the files starts from 0.
	    
	    	\n\n1.7.1:
	    	\nBetter support to Portuguese.
	    	\nMinor fixes.
	    	
	    	\n\n1.7:
	    	\nSave raw data in a CSV file.
	    
	    	\n\n1.6:
        	\nAdded support to the Portuguese language.
        	\nThanks to Rodrigo Hohl for translation.
        	
	        \n\n1.5:
	        \nOptimized for Kindle Fire and tablet with 7-inch screen.
	        \nAdded possibility to move the app to the SD card.
	        \nNew graphical interface.
	        
	        \n\n1.4:
	        \nAs suggested by a user, increased the size of the graphs in the pdf file.
	        \nImproved definition of menu icons.
	        \nImproved volume control.
	        \nFixed misprints.
	        
	        \n\n1.3:
	        \nIn order to help the researcher to study this test, 
	        it is now possible to display the progression of the selections.
	        
	        \n\n1.2:
	        \nThe application, maintaining the previous features, is now free:
	        we have chosen to promote the diffusion and circulation 
	        in order to be able to improve it and validate it through a larger number of feedback.
	        For those who deem it appropriate, we have introduced the possibility of making a donation.
	        
	        \n\n1.1:
	        \nAdded sound and vibration (vibration is not available for Motorola Xoom).
	</string>
	<string name="contatore_selezioni">Counter selections</string>
	<string name="contatore_selezioni_summary">Shows the progression of the selected cards</string>
	<string name="key_contatore_carte">KEY_CONTATORE_CARTE</string>
	<string name="selezione_n">Selection n:</string>
	<string name="app_name_min">IGT</string>
	<string name="spiegazione">Explanation:</string>
	<string name="vuoi_terminare_test">Want to quit?</string>
	<string name="si">Yes</string>
	
	<string name="my_continue">Continue</string>
	<string name="trial">trial</string>
	<string name="deck">deck</string>
	<string name="css_name">name</string>
	<string name="css_reward">reward</string>
	<string name="css_penalty">penalty</string>
	<string name="css_gain">gain</string>
	<string name="css_total">total</string>
	<string name="css_hh_mm_ss">hh_mm_ss</string>
	<string name="css_date">YYYY_MM_DD</string>
	<string name="css_response_time">response_time</string>
	<string name="css_touch_speed">touch_speed</string>
	<string name="css_pressure">pressure</string>
	<string name="css_pressure_style">pressure_style</string>
	
	<string name="touch_test_button_label">Pressure Test</string>
	<string name="touch_pressure">pressure:</string>
	<string name="pressure_style">pressure style:</string>
	<string name="touch_pressure_title">Touch Pressure</string>
	<string name="touch_speed">touch speed (ms):</string>
	
	<string name="detects_the_pressure">Detect the pressure</string>
	<!-- <string name="detects_the_pressure_info">Information about the pressure measurement 
	    								on touch screen devices</string> -->
	<string name="detects_the_pressure_info">Detecting the style of the touch
	    								on touch screen devices</string>	    								
	    								
	<string name="detects_the_pressure_text_info">
	    Some experimental measurements are introduced in order to detect 
	    the touch style of the subjects: the pressure on the screen, the pressure style,
	    the touch speed.
	    
	    \nThe pressure measurement on Android is device dependent:
	    not all devices support the pressure detection and devices that support 
	    can be calibrated differently and return different values. 
	    
	    When supported, the value is normalized to a range from 0.0 to 1.0, although values higher 
		than 1.0 may be generated depending on the calibration of the input device.
		
		The pressure can be measured in two moments: when the finger begins the contact 
		with the screen and when the finger stops the contact: the data saved in the CSV 
		file is the average of these two values.	
		When not supported, always returns the value 1.0.
		
		\nMoreover, for every touch, it is recorded a second measure called \"Pressure style\" which can 
		take only three values: 
		LOW_HIGH (when the initial pressure of the the touch is less than the final pressure),
		HIGH_LOW (when the initial pressure is greater than the final)
		and EQUAL (when the two pressures are equal).
		
		\nTo detect the style of the touch with a measure separated from the pressure,
		and therefore available on any device, is recorder the \"Touch speed\": for each touch, 
		for how many milliseconds the finger is in contact with the screen. 
		
		\n\nSumming up, the use of data related to the pressure may have value only if the device supports 
		the detection of the pressure and the test is performed by all the subjects using the same device.
		\nTherefore, recording and saving the pressure in the CSV file is an option that should be 
		enabled in the Settings menu (is not recorded by default).
		
		\n\nFor testing and understanding these measures, you can select the option 
		of displaying in the home screen a button that detects and displays the Pressure,
		the Pressure style and the Touch speed.			 
	</string>	    								

	<string name="record_the_pressure">Record the pressure</string>	
	<string name="test_button_label">Test button</string>	
	<string name="show_test_button_text">Show the button to test pressure
	    in the main screen</string>		     
	     
	<string name="csv_file_info_title">CSV file</string>
	<string name="csv_file_info_text">Summary of the data saved in the CSV file</string>	
	     
	     
	
	 
</resources>
